A Guide to the Summer Session, Office of the Dean, General Records, [1953] 1960-1979
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Summer Session, Office of the Dean, General Records [1953] 1960-1979
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-13/1/3.851
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student and employee records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.) and the Freedom of Information Act (F.O.I.A.). In addition, the collection may contain confidential donor information.
Acquisition Information
This collection was an archival transfer from the Office of the Dean, 1985 October 10.
Scope and Content
Records accumulated chiefly during the tenure of director Ralph W. Cherry include files on the budget, committees, planning, and research fees and salaries.
Contents List
- Analysis of Cost of Instruction, 1969 (Box 1)
- Association of University Summer Sessions: List of Members Coming, 1968-1971, 2 folders. (Box 1)
- Budget, 1960-1967 (Box 1)
- Budget (Excluding Education), 1966-1968 (Box 1)
- Budget, 1968 (Box 1)
- Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
- Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
- Budget, 1970-1972 (Box 2)
- Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
- Budget, 1971-1974 (Box 2)
- Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
- Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
- Budget Planning, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
- Calendar Study for Summer Session, Education, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
- Calendar, 1972 (Box 2)
- Claims, 1973 (Box 2)
- Commencement, 1961-1968 (Box 2)
- Committee (Old), 1953-1964 (Box 2)
- Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
- Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
- Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
- Committee: Notes and Statistics for 1967, 1968-1974 (Box 2)
- Cost Income Analysis, 1965 (Box 3)
- Disciplinary Actions, 1962-1968 (Box 3)
- General, 1956-1973 (Box 3)
- General, 1968 (Box 3)
- General, 1968 (Box 3)
- General, 1969 (Box 3)
- General, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
- Planning, 1967 (Box 4)
- Planning, 1970 (Box 4)
- Reading Center, 1970 (Box 4)
- Resident Staff Program, 1972 (Box 4)
- Research Fees and Salaries, 1967 (Box 4)
- Research Fees and Salaries, 1968 (Box 4)
- Salaries, etc., 1966-1979 (Box 4)
- Scholarships, General, 1962-1971 (Box 4)
- Special Courses, 1969 (Box 4)
- Tuition, Fees, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
- U. Va. Policies, 1969 (Box 4)